magic-kinder.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy - Magic Kinder - Magic Kinder

## Last Updated: March 2018

To view our practices regarding children, please click here.

Ferrero International S.A., the holding company of Ferrero Group ("Ferrero"), has conceived the Magic Kinder website ("Website") to provide parents with interesting information on the Magic Kinder App. By using our service you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, which describes our practices related to the use, storage and disclosure of any information we may collect from or about you through the Website. We take your trust and privacy very seriously and therefore we aim to process as little personal data as necessary, committing ourselves to a proper and legitimate processing of the same. "Processing" means using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information. Ferrero reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice. This Privacy Policy is not a contract and does not create any legal rights or obligations.

The Website processes data for the purpose of (i) operating and improving the service and (ii) to follow up on abuse reports and cooperate with law enforcement. We do NOT sell or otherwise distribute any personal data (if collected) to third parties and will not send you any commercial proposals unless expressly authorized to do so. To evaluate the use of our service as well as for statistical purposes, only anonymized data shall be used.

We do NOT collect Personal Data from User of our Website.

The Website may collect certain information automatically when you surf the Website, including, but not limited to, the type of device you use, your devices unique device ID, the IP address of your device, your operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the Website. The Website may access certain device information and/or components automatically. This collection is only for the purpose of providing the services within the Website you choose to use. This information is not linked to personal information about the user. We may work with analytics companies to help us understand how the Website is being used, such as the frequency and duration of usage.

The Website does not collect precise information about the location of your device.

On a normal basis, only aggregated, anonymized data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the Website and our service. We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

We may disclose User Automatically Collected Information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;
  * with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement.

If Ferrero is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information.

We do NOT work with third party advertising networks. We may only promote our Magic Kinder App via internet advertising on the Website. If you click on such an advertisement and navigate directly to the iTunes App Store or other platform, non-identifying information such as your phone's device ID may be sent to the advertising network, so that they and we may track the effectiveness (i.e., conversions) of our advertising. In addition to conversion events, it might also be used for frequency capping, estimating the number of unique users, debugging, or security and fraud detection.

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We only use "technical" cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. To know how to set the Cookies and receive any further info about please check our  Cookie Policy

Ferrero has chosen Amazon Web Services, Inc. (AWS) as the cloud service provider to store your data. The Article 29 Working Party (the independent advisory board made up of representatives from the data protection authorities of all the EU Member States as well as from the European Commission) has approved the AWS Data Processing Agreement, which includes the Model Clauses. The Article 29 Working Party has found that the AWS Data Processing Agreement meets the requirements of the Directive with respect to Model Clauses. For more detail on the approval of the AWS Data Processing Agreement from the Article 29 Working Party, please visit: [ https://www.cnpd.public.lu/en/actualites/international/2015/03/AWS.html ](https://www.cnpd.public.lu/en/actualites/international/2015/03/AWS.html)

We do not use the Website to knowingly solicit data from or market to people aged under 16. However, if a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [ privacy@ferrero.com ](mailto:privacy@ferrero.com). We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time. In accordance with applicable laws such as the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) to learn more about COPPA, you may consult this simple one-page informational guide from the kidSAFE Seal Program: [ https://www.kidsafeseal.com/knowaboutcoppa.html](https://www.kidsafeseal.com/knowaboutcoppa.html)

Information security is important to Ferrero and we are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We have established physical, electronic, managerial and procedural safeguards to protect the information we collect, process and maintain. These safeguards are regularly reviewed to protect against unauthorized access, disclosure and improper processing of your information, and to maintain the accuracy and integrity of that data. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve the website. Please be aware that, although we endeavor to provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches. For technical and operational reasons, personal data can be transferred through servers which are located outside the European Union, where the European data protection rules are not applicable. Privacy regulations outside the EU might not provide the same high level of protection.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our website [ www.magic-kinder.com ](https://www.magic-kinder.com/) and update the date shown above. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we may notify you promptly and seek to obtain your prior consent, or the consent of a parent or legal guardian.

## Contact us

**For privacy related questions**

**By E-mail**

privacy@ferrero.com

**By Phone**

(for US only) at (800) 688-3552 FREE or (732) 764-9300

**By post**

**Ferrero International S.A.**

Attn. Group Privacy Officer

Findel Business Center - Complexe B

Rue de Trèves, L-2632 Findel

Luxembourg
